Contact

+85593392690 (Mobile) vorreakboth@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vorreakboth (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Integrated Systems
Systems Management
Systems Engineering Process

Languages

English

Central Khmer

Certifications

Start with Why: How Great Leaders Inspire Everyone to Take Action (Blinkist Summary)

Good to Great: Why Some Companies Make the Leap and Others Don't (Blinkist Summary)

When: The Scientific Secrets of Perfect Timing (Blinkist Summary)

Bored and Brilliant (Blinkist Summary)

Built to Last: Successful Habits of Visionary Companies (Blinkist Summary)

Vorreakboth Chhoeurn

System Engineer @ Mobile C&C | Cisco Certified Phnom Penh, Cambodia

Summary

As a System Engineer at Mobile C&C, I use my bachelor's degree in computer science and my skills in Linux Server, and System to deploy Core Banking System and Bakong System. I have over two years of experience in this role, and previously I worked as Android App Developer, iOS App Developer, and Linux System Administrator, where I gained valuable experience in mobile app development and server management. I am passionate about using technology to solve problems and create value for customers and stakeholders. I enjoy working with a diverse and collaborative team that shares my vision and values. I am always eager to learn new skills and technologies that can help me improve my performance and deliver quality results.

Experience

Mobile C&C (Cambodia) Co.,Ltd. System Engineer October 2021 – Present

Phnom Penh, Cambodia

Khonnect

10 months

Wordpress Developer March 2021 - October 2021 (8 months)

Using Wordpress CMS to build website

Linux System Administrator March 2021 - October 2021 (8 months)

- Deployed web application to Digital Ocean
- Deployed web application to AWS
- Setup TinyCP

Web Designer
January 2021 - October 2021 (10 months)

Design Website using Adobe XD

Kasegro Co., Ltd.

1 year 8 months

Software Tester

December 2019 - January 2021 (1 year 2 months)

Manual test the app before publishing new features

Mobile Application Developer

October 2019 - January 2021 (1 year 4 months)

- Involve to develop eCommerce app
- Fix bugs of the app
- Add new features to the app
- Deployed native app to play store and app store

UX & UI Designer

June 2019 - October 2019 (5 months)

Design mobile app using Adobe XD based on the requirement

ComeBackApp

6 months

Mobile Application Developer

June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months)

- Designed UI and UX for new features
- Implemented User Interface for mobile app
- Deployed native app to play store and app store

Software Tester

March 2019 - August 2019 (6 months)

Manual test the app to find errors

Software Localization

March 2019 - August 2019 (6 months)

- Translate string in mobile app
- Add localization to the text for translation

Best Life Product

1 year 2 months

Technical Trainer

October 2018 - March 2019 (6 months)

- Write documentation how to use the app

- Train staffs to use the app
- Update the app based on feedback from client

Android Developer

May 2018 - October 2018 (6 months)

- Scan qr-code for login
- Store the records of operation
- Display reports from data that has been recorded

Laravel Developer

May 2018 - October 2018 (6 months)

- Make API for login with qr-code
- Make API for android app to store data
- Make API for android app to display reports

UX & UI Designer

February 2018 - May 2018 (4 months)

- Work with General Manager to know about operation
- Make System Requirements Specification based on operation
- Design UX & UI based on System Requirements Specification

Education

Royal University of Phnom Penh

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2015 - 2019)